JASON A. ARRITT

4700 Woodridge Drive, Raleigh, North Carolina 27612 (805) 550-3734

jason.a arritt@gmail.com

OBJECTIVE

Obtain a position as a full-stack web developer.

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

A dedicated professional experienced in computers and networking, as well as in the protection of personnel and property. Proficient at maintaining good relationships with coworkers and the public. Equally competent working alone and as a member of a team. Confident in exercising initiative and solving complex problems.

 Cisco Certified Network Associate 	Secret Clearance	Team Leader
 United States Army 	5 Years Active Duty	Highly Adaptable
 Client and Team Focused 	 Experience with C++, Python, and Linux 	 20 years of experience with Computers and Home Networks

EXPERIENCE

Airborne Infantryman, United States Army, Fort Bragg, NC 2013 – Present

- Aided in the liberation of Mosul, Iraq from ISIS, 2017
- Supervised and led teams in varying high stress situations with ever changing timelines and objectives
- Mentored new personnel in the different skills and tactics relative to their respective positions
- Developed new standard operating procedure for the clearing of mortar resistant bunkers
- Assisted in the capture of 5 enemy personnel and their military vehicle within 3 hours of entering "The Box" (Joint Readiness Training Center)

Sales Associate/Cashier, Big 5 Sporting Goods, Pismo Beach, CA, 2012 – 2013

- Managed store inventory and restocked items when shipments were received
- · Achieved correct cash drawer totals at the end of every shift
- Assisted customers in the locating and purchasing of various sporting goods
- Maintained a clean and inviting environment for customers to shop in

JASON A. ARRITT

PAGE 2

EDUCATION & TRAINING

- Cisco Certified Network Associate, May 2018
- Cisco Certified Entry Networking Technician, March 2018
- Currently learning Python programming language, began study while deployed in Iraq, self-taught, 2017
- Fayetteville Technical Community College, 19 semester credits towards Associates in Science, Fayetteville, NC
- DeVry University, 59 semester credits in Game and Simulation Programming with emphasis in C++ programming language, San Diego, CA
- Combat Life Savers (Plus), 40 hours
- Team Leader University, 40 hours
- SFA Foreign Weapons Course, 80 hours
- Advanced Rifle Marksmanship, 60 hours
- Explosive Breachers Course, 80 hours
- Modern Army Combatives Program level 1, 40 hours

ACHIEVEMENTS

- Army Commendation Medal Iraq 2017
- Combat Infantryman Badge Iraq 2017
- Operation Inherent Resolve Iraq 2017
- Good Conduct Medal 2016